<resources>
    <string name="app_name">IHSA Stable</string>
    <string name="app_logo_desc">IHSA logo</string>

    <!--    <string name = "hyperlink" ><a href = "https://www.ihsainc.com/about-us/general-information">IHSA_General_Information</a></string>-->
    <string name="textview"><b>IHSA MISSION</b>\n
\n

The mission of the IHSA is to provide equestrian competition for all college and university students regardless of riding level, gender, race, sexual  orientation or financial status. The IHSA is dedicated to promoting sportsmanship, horsemanship and academic excellence.\n
        \n
        <b>ABOUT IHSA COMPETITION</b>\n
        \n
\t IHSA welcomes beginners through advanced riders in the hunter and Western disciplines to compete individually or on a team. Men and women compete with and against each other.

IHSA eliminates the expenses of horse ownership. Horses are furnished by host colleges and are chosen by drawing lots. The use of personal tack is not allowed and schooling is not permitted. The format fairly tests the horsemanship of the athletes.Divisions range from Beginner to the Open Division for the more experienced riders.Full-time undergraduate students of member colleges or alumni who competed in the IHSA as undergraduates are eligible to compete. Riders qualify for the National Championship Horse Show (Nationals) through a point system. During the year, contestants accumulate points at their IHSA local shows to qualify for the Regional Finals in their respective divisions. The top two riders in each class of the Regional Finals move forward to the Zone Finals. The top two competitors in each class at Zones qualify for Nationals.Each region’s high-point team competes head to head with the other high point teams in its Zone for the right to represent the Zone for National champion team honors of winning the Collegiate Cup in the hunter seat division and the American Quarter Horse Association (AQHA) Trophy in the Western division.Regional high point riders are eligible for the National Individual Championship. The US Equestrian/Cacchione Cup is awarded to the National Individual hunter seat high-point rider. The AQHA Cup winner receives a saddle and a scholarship. The National Reining Horse Association (NRHA) awards a Morrison Bronze trophy to the Individual Open Reining Horsemanship class winner.Many IHSA competitors have gone on to play significant roles in the equestrian industry and in business.

        \n
        \n
        <b>IHSA HISTORY</b>
        \n
        \n
        The Intercollegiate Horse Shows Association was established in 1967 by Robert Cacchione while an 18-year-old sophomore attending Farleigh Dickinson University in Teaneck, New Jersey. Cacchione developed the prototype competition program with the help of his professor and renowned horseman Jack Fritz.
        Launched with just two colleges competing in hunter seat equitation, the IHSA was praised for its innovative competition format and quickly caught on. In 1979 the Western divisions premiered at the IHSA National Championship Horse Show (Nationals). In 1999 IHSA Inc. was established as a nonprofit organization.


        The early shows were judged by great horsemen, like Frank Chapot and Michael Page. Originally, Nationals were held at various college facilities.


        IHSA now encompasses 40 Regions in 8 Zones with over 400 member colleges in 45 states and Canada and represents 10,000 members in hunter seat equitation on the flat and over fences, Western horsemanship, ranch riding and reining. To support the size of the organization, IHSA now requires major venues like Harrisburg, the Kentucky Horse Park and Los Angeles Equestrian Center for its National Championships.

        Some of the most notable riders in show jumping and the Western disciplines competed in the IHSA during their college years. Four-time Olympian and two-time Olympic gold medalist Beezie Madden competed for Southern Seminary and won the Cacchione Cup in 1984. Olympic gold medalist Peter Wylde won the Cacchione Cup in 1986 while he attended Tufts University.

        \n

\n
        \n

        <b>Get to know more about IHSA: </b>
        <a href="https://www.ihsainc.com/about-us/general-information">IHSA_General_Information</a>
        \n
    </string>

    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="title_activity_schedule">scheduleActivity</string>
    <string name="dummy_button">Dummy Button</string>
    <string name="dummy_content">DUMMY\nCONTENT</string>

</resources>
